<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE PluginInfo [
<!ENTITY SrcPx "https://visumap.github.io/images/">
]>
<PluginInfo xmlns="urn:VisuMap.Technologies:VisuMap">

<PluginList>

<Plugin Name="Clip Recorder" Version="1.13" Source="&SrcPx;ClipRecorder.zip">
A plugin to record map snapshots during the MDS learning process.
</Plugin>

<Plugin Name="Binary Metrics" Version="2.3" Source="&SrcPx;BinaryMetrics.zip">
A collection of metrics for binary data (e.g. Jacard, Tanimoto distances.) with support for sparse set encoding.
</Plugin>

<Plugin Name="Numeric Metrics" Version="1.6" Source="&SrcPx;NumericMetrics.zip">
A collection of metrics for numerical data (e.g. harmonical mean, city-block distance.)
</Plugin>

<Plugin Name="Graph Metrics" Version="1.3" Source="&SrcPx;GraphMetrics.zip">
A collection of metrics for graph structural data (a la adjacency matrix imported from sdf files, metrics include shortest path distance, resistance distances.)
</Plugin>

<Plugin Name="Custom Importer" Version="2.13" Source="&SrcPx;CustomImporter.zip">
A collection of custom importers. Supported file formats: arff, cel, sdf, mol, fcs, mtx, mtx.gz and a configuable CSV format filter.
</Plugin>

<Plugin Name="Wave Transforms" Version="1.3" Source="&SrcPx;WaveTransforms.zip">
A set of wave transformations like Fourier and Wavelet transformations. See the help menu of VisuMap "About WaveTransforms" for more information after installed this plugin.
</Plugin>

<Plugin Name="MVA Plugin" Version="2.5" Source="&SrcPx;VmMultivariateAnalysis.zip">
Multivariate analysis: LDA (linear discriminant analysis); PLS (partial least squares) and CCA (canonic correlation analysis.
</Plugin>

<Plugin Name="Data Generator" Version="1.5" Source="&SrcPx;DataGenerator.zip">
A plugin to generates various kind of dataset for experimental purposes.
</Plugin>

<Plugin Name="Data Cleansing" Version="1.11" Source="&SrcPx;DataCleansing.zip">
A plugin for data cleansing services.
</Plugin>

<Plugin Name="Custom Glyphs" Version="1.6" Source="&SrcPx;CustomGlyphSets.zip">
Some custom bitmap glyhsets.
</Plugin>

<Plugin Name="Genetic Analysis" Version="1.4" Source="&SrcPx;GeneticAnalysis.zip">
Plugin for various services related to genetics. Imorter for fasta, fastq and beggraph files.
</Plugin>

<Plugin Name="Data Modeling" Version="1.4" Source="&SrcPx;DataModeling.zip">
Data modeling with deep artificial neural networks. TensorFlow version 1.12 must be installed.
</Plugin>

<Plugin Name="Single Cell Analysis" Version="1.1" Source="&SrcPx;SingleCellAnalysis.zip">
Services to facilitate single cell RNA sequence (scRNA-seq) analysis. Implements the SC.DualEmbedding and SC.DualCorrelation distances functions.
</Plugin>

<Plugin Name="Heatmap Atlas" Version="1.1" Source="&SrcPx;HeatmapAtlas.zip">
Scripts to create heatmap for single cell RNA expression data with dual sorting, mapping and clustering. 
The module also provides services to import Loom, H5, H5AD and MarketMatrix (mtx) files.
</Plugin>

<Plugin Name="VisuModelling" Version="1.2" Source="&SrcPx;VisuModelling.zip">
Scripts to create deep learning models for embedding and clustering. This plugin uses tensorflow library, and optionally CUDA/GPU services.
</Plugin>

<Plugin Name="DataLink" Version="1.2" Source="&SrcPx;DataLink.zip">
Plugin to help python programs to communicate with VisuMap. A numpy file importer is also included. 
</Plugin>

</PluginList>

<AppList>
<AppInfo Name="VisuMap" Version="6.0" Builder="977" Source="&SrcPx;VisuMap6_0.msi" Size="14156288"/>
</AppList>

</PluginInfo>
